<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News Releases - RDFa Lite</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 13:48:33 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 13:48:33 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.1.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>MP Opitz to Make an Announcement Regarding Humanitarian Assistance in Somalia</title>
        <description></description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2017/07/23/media-FATD/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2017/07/23/media-FATD/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Harper Government Invests in Recreational Fisheries Conservation Projects in Newfoundland and Labrador</title>
        <description>  &lt;section&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;The Government of Canada to invest up to $5.5 million to restore recreational fisheries habitat through the National Conservation Plan&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Honourable Gail Shea, Minister of Fisheries and Oceans, today announced investments by the Government of Canada to support conservation projects in Newfoundland and Labrador through the Recreational Fisheries Conservation Partnerships Program (RFCPP). Under the second round of the program, over $160,000 is awarded to five projects in the province to rebuild, restore and rehabilitate fish habitat.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Recreational Fisheries Conservation Partnerships Program was announced in Economic Action Plan 2013 to support fisheries habitat restoration projects led by recreational fishing and angling groups, as well as conservation organizations. Given its early success and high demand, an additional investment in Economic Action Plan 2014 increased the funding available through the program to a total investment of $25 million.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;On May 15, 2014, the National Conservation Plan was launched to provide a more coordinated approach to conservation efforts across the country. Since 2006, the Government of Canada has taken important steps to conserve and restore our country&amp;rsquo;s natural environment and connect Canadians to our rich natural heritage. To date, the Recreational Fisheries Conservation Partnerships Program has invested nearly $6 million (Round I), in 94 fisheries habitat restoration projects across Canada and funding to support up to an additional 127 projects (Round II) is currently underway. The window to apply for Round III funding is now open and applications will be accepted until August 15, 2014&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/section&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2014/07/23/FOC/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2014/07/23/FOC/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Government of Canada consults with stakeholders in Toronto to help shape new Labour Market Development Agreements</title>
        <description>  &lt;p&gt;Scott Armstrong, Parliamentary Secretary to the Minister of Employment and Social Development, today hosted a roundtable on how to strengthen the Labour Market Development Agreements (LMDAs). This is part of a series of roundtables that Mr. Armstrong will host, in cooperation with provincial and territorial governments, across Canada.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;As part of its plan for creating jobs, economic growth, and long-term prosperity, the Government of Canada is committed to strengthening LMDAs to reorient training toward labour market demand. It is expected that the new LMDAs will better connect Canadians with available jobs by ensuring they have access to training for the skills employers need. Funded through the Employment Insurance (EI) program, the Government of Canada transfers over $2 billion annually to the provinces and territories through the LMDAs to provide skills training to EI clients and employment services to all unemployed Canadians.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The roundtables give governments, employers, and other stakeholders an opportunity to discuss how to make the LMDAs more employer-driven and responsive to the needs of the labour market. The roundtables also give the Government of Canada valuable insight on local skills shortages and gaps.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2014/07/23/ESDC/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2014/07/23/ESDC/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Canada Congratulates Joko Widodo on Winning Indonesia&#39;s Presidential Election</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Foreign Affairs Minister John Baird today welcomed the official announcement by the Indonesian National Electoral Commission that Mr. Joko Widodo and his running mate, Mr. Jusuf Kalla, have won Indonesia’s 2014 presidential election, held on July 9.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Canada warmly congratulates president-elect Joko Widodo and his campaign on their success. We are optimistic about Indonesia’s future, and I plan to visit there again in the very near future,” said Baird.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Indonesia is the world’s third-largest democracy, with 190 million registered voters. Today’s result underscores the impressive strides that Indonesia and its institutions have made in the 10 years since its first democratic elections.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2014/07/22/FATD2/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2014/07/22/FATD2/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Minister Fast Announces Next Round of Negotiations Toward Canada-Japan Free Trade Agreement</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Honourable Ed Fast, Minister of International Trade, today announced the sixth round of negotiations toward a Canada-Japan Economic Partnership Agreement (&lt;abbr&gt;EPA&lt;/abbr&gt;). The negotiations will take place in Ottawa from July 28 to July 31, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A joint study on the possibility of a Canada-Japan economic partnership agreement concluded that a trade agreement with Japan could boost Canada’s economy by $3.8 billion annually, which is equivalent to the creation of almost 25,000 new jobs, and increase Canada’s exports to Japan by as much as 67 percent. An agreement would strengthen bilateral trade and investment opportunities in many areas, benefiting all sectors of the economy, including agri-food products, forestry and wood products, fish and seafood, manufacturing, natural resources and financial services.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2014/07/22/FATD/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2014/07/22/FATD/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>MP Kerr to Participate in Grand Opening of Annapolis Royal Wharf</title>
        <description></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2014/07/18/ACOA/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2014/07/18/ACOA/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>TransLink makes commuting by bicycle more convenient</title>
        <description>                &lt;section&gt;
                    &lt;h2&gt;Indoor Secure Bike Parking area opens at Main Street-Science World Station&lt;/h2&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;Just in time for Bike to Work Week (&lt;time datetime=&quot;2014-05-26&quot;&gt;May 26&lt;/time&gt; to &lt;time datetime=&quot;2014-06-01&quot;&gt;June 1, 2014&lt;/time&gt;), TransLink is pleased to announce the opening of the new Secure Bike Parking area at Main Street-Science World SkyTrain Station. The Secure Bike Parking area is located indoors, inside the newly upgraded east stationhouse, and boasts 86 bike racks, more than four times the number of bike lockers that used to sit outside the station.&lt;/p&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;The new Secure Bike Parking area is a first of its kind on TransLink’s transit network. The facility is accessible by key card and costs just $1 a day up to a maximum of $8 a month, plus a one-time $8 registration fee. The program is also expanding. Secure Bike Parking areas will replace bike lockers at some of TransLink’s busiest stations and bus loops over the next few years.&lt;/p&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;Main Street-Science World is one of seven stations along the Expo Line being upgraded with funding from federal and provincial partners. The station upgrades include an expanded east stationhouse, new escalators, stairs and elevator, a new west station entrance and the Secure Bike Parking area.&lt;/p&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;The budget for all the Main Street-Science World Station upgrades, including the Secure Bike Parking area, is $33 million. The Government of Canada is contributing $7 million from the Building Canada Fund, the Province of British Columbia is contributing $14 million, and TransLink is contributing $12 million.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/section&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2014/05/26/transport/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2014/05/26/transport/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
